Finding Aid for Robert C. Metcalf papers, 1950-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Projects by Job Number
    - Job 0-52, Mr. and Mrs. Robert C. Metcalf 1052 Arlington Boulevard, Ann Arbor, MI, 1952
      - Presentation Boards, 5 14x11 & 1 20x15-inch boards (Map-case 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (slide boxes 0 & 00)
    - Job No. 1-53, Mr. and Mrs. H. Richard Crane, 830 Avon Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1953
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 12x8, 1 12x10, 2 12x13, 2 13x12, 1 14.5x12, 1 15.5x11.5, 1 16x12, 5 17x12, 9 18x12, 1 20x11.5, 1 21x11, 7 21x12, 2 21x13, 1 21x15, 2 21x16, 1 22x17, 1 23.5x12, 31 24x18,1 25x12, 1 25x15, 1 26x12, 2 30x20, & 13 34x20-inch drawings; blueprints, pencil on vellum, pencil on tracing paper, colored pencil on paper, colored pencil on vellum, pen on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client file, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Graphics file (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1953 Professor and Mrs. H.S. Bull, Ann Arbor Hills, MI, 1953
      (alterations)
      - Architectural Drawings, 6 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, details (Map-case 1)
    - Job No. Misc. 1953 Professor Catherine B. Heller, 1317 Pontiac Trail, Ann Arbor, MI, 1953
      (addition)
      - Architectural Drawings, 5 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client file (Box 1)
    - Job No. 2-54, Professor and Mrs. Elman R. Service, 401 Awixa Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1954
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 2-54 & 61-60, 40 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client file, 2 folders (Box 1)
      - Graphics file (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 3-54, Professor and Mrs. Philip J. Elving 2309 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1954
      - Architectural Drawings, 19 24x18 & 10 36x24-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 4-54, Professor and Mrs. David M. Dennison, 2511 Hawthorn Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1954
      - Architectural Drawings, 40 24x18-inch drawings: pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Presentation Board, 1 30x20-inch board (Map-case 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 5-54, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur J. Stockon, 223 Deuber Avenue, SW., Canton, OH 1954
      - Architectural Drawings, 29 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 6-54, Professor and Mrs. George Brymer Williams 2316 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1954
      - Architectural Drawings, 60 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Presentation Board, 1 30x20-inch board (Map-case 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. Misc. 1954 Dr. James P. Warren, Office, 309 W. Michigan Avenue, Ypsilanti, MI, 1954
      (remodel not built)
      - Architectural Drawings, 12 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
    - Job No. Misc. 1954 Morton Arboretum Small House Competition, Lisle, IL, 1954
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Presentation Board, 1 14.5x14.5-inch board (Map-case 11)
    - Job No. 7-55, Attorney and Mrs. Franklin C. Forsythe, 500 Barton Shore Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 7-55 & 57-60, 49 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 8-55, Professor and Mrs. Franklin G. Moore 2255 Glendaloch Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1955
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 8-55 & 133-98, 34 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 1)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Jamie and Cheryl Seguino (Job 133-98) Client File (Box 1)
    - Job No. 9-55, Professor and Mrs. Lawrence W. Jones, 447 Hilldale Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 9-55 & 56-60, 25 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 10-55, Mr. Robert Wollam, Restaurant, US Highway 12, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 6 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; floor plans (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 11-55, Professor and Mrs. Kent M. Terwilliger, 632 Wagner Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 23 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x15-inch board (Map-case 11)
    - Job No. 12-55, Gamma Phi Beta, Sorority House 1520 S. University, Ann Arbor, MI, 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 50 24x18 & 21 36x24-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, colored pencil on vellum, colored pencil on paper; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 13-55, Mr. and Mrs. Maurice B. Hodges 2715 Parkridge Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 28 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans; elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 14-55, Mr. and Mrs. C. Russell King, Scio Township, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 15 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 1)
      - Graphics File (Box 1)
    - Job No. 15-55, Professor and Mrs. Charles W. Phillips, 912 Aberdeen Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1955
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 15-55 & 110-83, 42 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 16-55, Volkswagen Agency 4500 Jackson Road, Jackson, MI, 1955
      - Architectural Drawings, 12 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. Misc. 1955 Community Youth Center, Porcelain Enamel Competition, Architectural Forum, 1955
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x14-inch board; outsized (Map-case 11)
    - Job No. 17-56, Mr. and Mrs. Robert B. O'Hara 1620 Sheridan Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 11 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Box 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 18-56, Mr. and Mrs. Russell Sponseller 3626 Waynesburg Road, Canton, OH, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 21 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 19-56, Attorney and Mrs. Filmer Paradise, 495 Hillspur Road, Barton Hills, MI 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 22 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 20-56, Dr. E.W. Reynolds 2948 Parkridge Drive, Scio Township, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 22 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; renderings; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 21-56, Dr. and Mrs. Ralph W. Gerard, 15 Harvard Place, Ann Arbor, MI 1956
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 21-56 & 135-99, 14 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Robert Eckstein (Job 135-99) Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 22-56, Mr. and Mrs. Lloyd T. Williams 1101 Martin Place, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 2)
        (missing due to water damage in 1994 Metcalf office flood)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 23-56, Mr. Albert Duckek (I) 1119 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 23-56 & 130-96, 27 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Attorney Lawrence W. Waggoner (Job 130-96) Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 24-56, Mr. David Vaughn, Owosso, MI 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 4 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x15-inch board (Map-case 11)
    - Job No. 25-56, Mark VIII House, Inter Cooperative Council, 917 S. Forest Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 16 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 2)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 26-56, Mr. and Mrs. Damon C. Woods 1041 Belmont Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 26-56 & 143-02, 48 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (slide boxes 1 & 6)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Dr. and Mrs. Barry Siegel & Mr. and Mrs. Evan Cohen (Job 143-02) Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 27-56, Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth Patterson 1605 Harbal Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings, 39 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Presentation Boards, 1 15x12 & 2 20x15-inch boards (Map-case 11)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Professor Dave Hollinden & Ms. Audra Wenzlow Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 28-57, Dr. and Mrs. Kenneth Magee 1109 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 1956
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 28-57 & Nordman, 27 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Presentation Boards, 2 20x15-inch boards (Map-case 12)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Professor and Mrs. Christer Nordman Client File (Box 2)
        - Mr. Paul C. McCoy and Ms. Shelley Steele (Box 2)
          (see Job 136-99 for client file, drawings, & slides)
    - Job No. 29-57, Mr. and Mrs. William H. Lyon, 540 N. Chipman Street, Owosso, MI 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 22 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 30-57, Mr. and Mrs. William E. Riskey, Whitmore Lake, MI 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 14 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 31-57, Dr. and Mrs. Stefan S. Fajans 2485 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 26 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Photographs on CD (Box 11)
      - Presentation Board, 1 20x15-inch board (Map-case 12)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 32-57, Mr. and Mrs. Norman N. Gottlieb, Brookside Drive, Flint, MI 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 19 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 33-57, Dr. and Mrs. Edmund S. Botch 1053 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 38 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 2)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. Jarvis Franzlau Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 34-57, Mr. Jack R. Weid 2509 S. State Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 10 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 2)
    - Job No. 35-57, Church of the Good Shepherd, United Church of Christ 2145 Independence Boulevard, Ann Arbor, MI, 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 42 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File, 4 folders (Box 2)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Presentation Boards, 2 13.5x27, 1 18x12, 3 20x15, 1 20x27, 1 22x28, & 3 30x20-inch boards; outsized (Map-case 12)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 36-57, Professor and Mrs. Marshall D. Sahlins 2466 Newport Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1957
      - Architectural Drawings, 29 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 1)
    - Job No. Misc. 1957 Mr. and Mrs. Fred Black, 804 Berkshire Road, Ann Arbor, 1957
      (remodel)
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 24x18-inch drawing; pencil on vellum; details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 37-58, Mr. and Mrs. Paul Harvey, 613 Main Street, East Tawas, MI 1958
      (designed for Bay City, MI; built in East Tawas, MI)
      - Architectural Drawings, 31 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, blueline; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Jim Mielke (1989) Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 38-57, Mr. and Mrs. William Willits 1911 Packard Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1958
      - Architectural Drawings, 14 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 39-58, Mr. and Mrs. Millard H. Pryor, 715 Spring Valley, Barton Hills, MI 1958
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 39-58 & 137-99, 47 24x18 & 3 18x12-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File, 3 folders (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide boxes 1 & 6)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. Peter Newhouse (Job 137-99) Client File (Box 3)
        - Mr. and Mrs. Uwe Pleban Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 40-58, Attorney and Mrs. Robert M. Campbell 1029 Chestnut Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1958
      - Architectural Drawings, 44 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 3)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 41-58, Professor and Mrs. Mischa Titiev, 910 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI 1958
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 41-58 & 55-60, 31 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, pencil on paper; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 42-58, Mr. and Mrs. Jacques Les Strang 2427 Londonderry Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1958
      - Architectural Drawings, 53 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum, pencil on paper; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Presentation Boards, 3 20x16-inch boards (Map-case 13)
      - Slides (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
        (see Box 12, slide box 2)
    - Job No. 43-58, Professor and Mrs. Everett S. Brown 2576 Devonshire Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1958
      - Architectural Drawings, 18 24x18 & 20 32x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 44-58, West Park Shelter, 213 Chapin Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1958
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18 & 12 30x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 45-59, Dr. and Mrs. Reed O. Dingman 1029 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 1 18x12, 7 24x18 & 23 30x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum, colored pencil on vellum, colored pencil on paper; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 4)
      - Client File, 2 folders (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 46-59, Mr. and Mrs. Hollis W. Peter 2649 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 46-59 & 112-86, 38 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Eric Stein (Job 112-86) Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 47-59, Mr. and Mrs. Robert W. Carr 3130 Dolph Drive, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 24 24x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
        (see also Job No. 144-02, Hurtado)
      - Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 48-59, Mr. and Mrs. Leslie A. Grimord, 19 Heatheridge Street, Ann Arbor, MI 1959
      - Architectural Drawings for Jobs 48-59, 66-61, & 126-95, 51 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Ms. Ruth Siegel (Job 126-95) Client File (Box 3)
    - Job No. 49-59, Dr. and Mrs. J. Max Busard 2361 Westwood Road, Muskegon, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 37 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 50-59, St. Andrew's United Church of Christ 7640 Ann Arbor Street, Dexter, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 12 24x18, 2 33x24, & 13 36x24-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details; outsized (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 3)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 51-59, Dr. and Mrs. Graham Chen, 119 Dixboro Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 37 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 3)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Reza Morshidi and Setareh Moazzami (Box 4)
          (see Job 149-05 for drawings, client and graphics files, & photographs)
    - Job No. 52-59, Dr. and Mrs. Ralph S. Moyer 2935 Hickory Lane, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 32 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, rendering, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Ed Yao (Box 4)
          (see Job 121-91 for drawings, client file, & graphics file)
    - Job No. 53-59, Mr. and Mrs. Harold E. Wilde 1305 Brooks Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 7 24x18 drawings; pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. Misc. 1959 Dr. and Mrs. Albert Furstenberg (Brigham), 2240 Belmont, Ann Arbor, MI, 1959
      - Architectural Drawings, 6 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on vellum; studies, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 4)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 54-60, Dr. and Mrs. Robert Emerick 3947 Shorewood Drive, Fremont, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 41 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 55-60, Professor and Mrs. Mischa Titiev, 910 Heatherway, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 5)
        (see Job 41-58, Titiev)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 56-60, Professor and Mrs. Lawrence W. Jones, 447 Hilldale Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 5)
        (see Job 9-55, Jones)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 57-60, Attorney and Mrs. Franklin C. Forsythe, 500 Barton Shore Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 5)
        (see Job 7-55, Forsythe)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 58-60, Mr. and Mrs. Robert W. Parry 2588 Hawthorn Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 9 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 59-60, Professor Alice Rhodes Mulchahey, 619 Turner Park Court, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 19 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 60-60, Professor and Mrs. Leonard A. Greenbaum, 374 Hilldale Drive, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      (not all additions built)
      - Architectural Drawings, 40 24x18-inch drawings; colored pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
        (includes subsequent additions without job numbers)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
      - Slides (Box 12)
    - Job No. 61-60, Professor and Mrs. Elman R. Service, 401 Awixa Road, Ann Arbor, MI 1960
      - Architectural Drawings (Map-case 5)
        (see Job 2-54, Service)
      - Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 62-60, Professor and Mrs. Arnold S. Tannenbaum 2521 Newport Road, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 33 24x18-inch drawings; blueline, pencil on vellum; studies, renderings, plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Graphics File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 63-60, Professor and Mrs. Frederick J. Beutler 1232 Bending Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960
      - Architectural Drawings, 15 24x18-inch drawings; pencil on paper, pencil on vellum; plans, elevations, sections, details (Map-case 5)
      - Client File (Box 4)
      - Subsequent Owner Alterations
        - Mr. and Mrs. Brian Nao Client File (Box 4)
    - Job No. 64-60, Dr. Lyle D. Elliott 1075 Chestnut Street, Ann Arbor, MI, 1960